



## Contact

pileliene.laima@gmail.com

+37067074438

Kretinga



### Links

My Linkedin

My Porfolio

# **Education**

- **Baltic Institute of Technology** Full stack developer Completed in 2024
- **Vilnius University** Master's degree in Molecular Biology Completed in 2018
- **Vilnius University** Bachelor's degree in Molecular Biology Completed in 2016

# Language



# Laima Pilelienė

## **Profile**

I am currently enrolled in the modular professional training program for Full Stack Developer at the Baltic Technology Institute. In a short span, I have rapidly acquired a diverse set of skills, gaining hands-on experience with projects involving HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, as well as React and Laravel frameworks. Now, I am ready to continue learning, prepared to take new challenges, and further enhance my capabilities through real-world practice and job opportunities.

# **Work Experience**

Feb 2018- June 2019 THERMO FISHER SCIENTIFIC BALTICS, VIInius

#### **Junior Scientist**

Independent experiment planning and execution (E-gel, NGS, qPCR). New product research and development (PCR, RT-PCR, RT-qPCR, qPCR). Analytical method development and validation, documentation preparation, product design verification and validation. Experimental data analysis and presentation to cross-functional team members and managers.

2014 - 2015 THERMO FISHER SCIENTIFIC BALTICS, VIlnius

## **Junior Bioanalyst**

Quality control laboratory: testing new product by various protocols and experiments (PCR, qPCR, Spectrometry, DNR, Protein electrophoresis, endotoxin testing, measuring enzymatic activities (by spectrophotometry, radiolabeling, fluorescence), enzymatic plate assay (ELISA)). Documentation preparation.

2014 - 2018

THERMO FISHER SCIENTIFIC BALTICS, VIInius

#### Intern

Designing and performing experiments by various laboratory equipment. Experimental data analysis, summarizing and presentation. Bachelor and Master research projects.

# Reference

Mantas Santockis

Mentor in Baltic Institute of Technology

Phone: +370 608 37119 Email: mantas@bit.lt

#### Evelina Čatrauskienė

Validation Manager at Thermo Fisher Scientific Baltics

Phone: +370 65445285

Email: evelina.catrauskiene@gmail.com